Sasaki.
I'm sorry, dog. I'm sorry today. I'm sorry tomorrow.
I'm sorry I was so mean to you.
But you always let me off the hook.
I love you. I'm sure he knows that.
I'll give you a stylish refill, thank you!
Thank you very much for taking time out of your busy schedule to join us today.
We will now hold the World Social Conference.
Oh, but there are quite a few.
Is that a wolf?
Is it a wolf?
I'm sorry, there's a wolf among the dogs.
Is this a mistake by the staff?
What do you think?
I don't think so.
It's still not Kevuku.
I know you were embarrassed during the test, but I hope your reactions are good.
Oh, my God.
Really?
Oh no.
I think there's going to be a character.
There's Mr. Kikori.
Kikori-san.
Mr. Kikori is here.
It's been a while.
Oh no.
Kikori-san's hair.
Oh, no, Kikori-san.
Oh, no.
He says a lot of things because he can't talk much.
Really.
I don't know what to do.
Oh no.
I hate it so much.
I thought I wasn't supposed to smile.
I guess it's okay to laugh a little.
I'm just going with my feelings.
I can't do this. I don't know if I can do this.
You know I'm a total prick, don't you?
I thought the link was appropriate, but...
Excuses are bad.
I'd say it's better if you can't speak.
Start!
Thank you very much for taking time out of your busy schedule to join us here today.
We will now deliberately hold an outside press conference.
I am Nanako Hirokawa, the leader of Fursta.
Even we, at the time of winter,
The song is called "Cat's Cat's Youth in Full Blossom,
We have sung not only about cats, but also about the feelings of dogs.
But from that point on, we started to brand ourselves as cat-centric,
We started branding ourselves as a cat only.
Shall I sing it once?
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule today to join the press.
Can I sing one more time?
No problem.
Let's sing one more time.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedules to join us today.
We will now have the Firster press conference.
I think we should have a press conference for the Fursta society.
I am Manako Kiyokawa, leader of Fursta.
At the time of our debut, we sang about the feelings of dogs as well as cats in our song "Inu Neko Seishun no Masutakari" ("Dogs, Cats, and Youth").
However, since then, our branding has become completely cat-centric, and we have not considered the feelings of dogs at all.
We are very sorry for that.
I am very sorry.
Oryx just made me do it.
We were deceived by adults.
From now on, we will renew our feelings and
And we will not forget everyone's feelings.
We will continue our activities.
I am truly sorry for what happened.
We will now hold an internal press conference.
Cut.
May I have one more?
Yes, ma'am.
I almost laughed at the end.
That's harsh.
Don't laugh.
We're all very busy today.
Thank you very much for coming today.
Thank you very much.
We will now have a balanced in-house press conference.
Did someone just speak?
You can film me once when I speak.
I'm very sorry about this.
I'm so sorry.
Bend the line...
Like this.
If you're careful, rie
It's going to be a cartoon game.
Cut!
That's the best I've ever had!
Bon appétit!
It's you. You're in danger of hitting a little too close to the mark.
So, the flow is that you guys start getting ready, and then you say you're mad at each other.
That's a strong habit.
Oh, man...
I'm out of the loop.
And that's where the members are.
"Wan wan wan wan, are you finished today?
He's saying, "Woof, woof, woof.
I don't know what he's saying.
Ah!
Cat.
There are a lot of VISUALTISTS here.
This is a no-no.
I really don't want to be offended if you laugh.
Please do!
Let's get to work!
Here we go.
It was playing next to me.
Yes, cut.
I was tricked by an adult.
Cut!
I think it's really good.
I think I might have been held down earlier.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
This is a little...
I can use this.
Ha-ha-ha!
Mimi's shaking.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Busy.
You're busy.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Where's the cat?
Thanks for coming.
Wow.
Cute. I'm here to clear up so much.
So cute.
I'm here to clear it.
We have friends. A lot of them.
Play Bikkuri Donkey.
Like this.
I'm going to drink tea.
Thank you very much for your cooperation in filming today.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you again.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Yay! Home!
That's great!
Amazing!
Good job!
It's really too fluffy.
Yay!
This could be real.
The room here is amazing.The room here is amazing.
Thank you.
You're just as I pictured you.
Oh, my God.
It's pretty bouncy.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good job.
Orimpi, orimpi, orimpi.
You made it by hand?
Wow.
Wow!
Let's work together again!
Cute head!
Cute head.
Do the pickle donkey.